matchrateplus.com 2012-09-19

# Match Rate Plus > Legal > Privacy Policy

MatchRatePLUS.com is committed to protect your privacy, and rigorous procedures have been implemented to ensure this. The following Privacy Policy provides information on how your personal information is collected and used.

**A. What this site does with the information it gathers/tracks:**  
MatchRatePLUS.com may offer several opportunities for visitors to register to become an Agent at no cost. Our site’s optional information requests forms that require your name, company, e-mail address, as well as information to help get your account created with us and our payment processor.

Information submitted by you within our website, will be used only by us in order to provide customer support to you, inform you of any new promotion or update of our website, provide to our partner processor, and/or to help you get enrolled as an Agent. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We use this information to send updates about our company and will contact you if requested or necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. We also track browser types to help us understand our visitors’ needs related to our website design. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. When you enter a contest or other promotional features we run for Agents from time to time, we ask for information such as your name, mailing address, daytime phone number and email address, so we can administer the contest and contact you to receive feedback regarding our product.

**B. Choice/Opt-out**  
There is no cost to become an Agent. You can can cancel by simply doing nothing or unsubscribing from our emails. If you sign up as Agent or Referral Partner, we request certain personally identifiable information from you. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and physical address). We use this information for promotion, contact, or support purposes.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter whether it is a promotional, support, or other related communication, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

We offer an opportunity to opt-out of promotional, support, and Agent related communication emails, by clicking on the unsubscribe link on the emails. Or, if it’s easier for you to write a letter to inform us that you’d like to unsubscribe from our newsletters, which will effectively remove you from MatchRatePLUS.com and our Agent program, you can write to us using a red crayon:

MatchRatePLUS.com  
ATTN: Customer Service Department  
4888 Davis Blvd  
Naples, FL 34104  
Phone: (239) 599 3033  
Fax: (239) 599 3034

Every email sent through MatchRatePLUS.com contains an easy, automated unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. To unsubscribe, you simply need to click the link at the bottom of the page in the unsubscribe area. You are immediately excluded from all future mailings.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**C. With whom this site shares information it gathers/tracks/shares:**  
We share aggregate statistics about our customer’s traffic patterns and reservations with our suppliers and partners, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information. Like most Web sites, there is certain information we automatically track, including the URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next, the browser you are using and your IP address.

Information gathered by our partner processor, as the name of the client, name of the company, phone number, email address, etc., is necessary for them to provide you with the ability to enroll into our Agent program and is needed in order for you to be compensated.

We use cookies to help users navigate efficiently between secure and non-secure pages of our site. Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they identify a user’s computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of a website if you do so. We link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

**D. Updating personally identifiable information:**  
We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. You have the option to register with MatchRatePLUS.com to become an Agent. You can update your personal information, subscriptions, or service package at any time by contacting our support department.

**E. Links to Other Sites:**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by MatchRatePLUS.com. Please be aware that MatchRatePLUS.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.

**F. Security:**  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once they receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email to our support department at: [Support@MatchRatePLUS.com](mailto:Support@MatchRatePLUS.com)

**G. How to Contact Us:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or would like more information about our company, please contact us at: [Support@MatchRatePLUS.com](mailto:Support@MatchRatePLUS.com), or send us a letter to:

MatchRatePLUS.com  
ATTN: Legal Department  
4888 Davis Blvd  
Naples, FL 34104  
Phone: (239) 599 3033  
Fax: (239) 599 3034

**H. Changes to our Privacy Policy:**  
This policy may be revised over time as new features are added to the web site. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site for information about revisions to our privacy policy.
